<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<info:toolkitInfoModel xmlns:common="http://www.ibm.com/xmlns/prod/streams/spl/common"
                       xmlns:info="http://www.ibm.com/xmlns/prod/streams/spl/toolkitInfo">
    <info:identity>
        <info:name>com.ibm.streamsx.eventstore</info:name>
    <info:description><![CDATA[
The Eventstore toolkit is an open source IBM Streams toolkit that provides adapters for the 
[https://www.ibm.com/products/db2-event-store|Db2 Event Store] database.

IBM Db2 Event Store is an in-memory database designed to rapidly ingest and analyze streamed data in event-driven applications. It provides the fabric for fast data with its ability to process massive volume of events in real-time, coupled with optimization for streamed data performance for advanced analytics and actionable insights.

**It provides the operators**
* `EventStoreSink` to insert tuple data 

**The EventStoreSink operator supports the following features**
* Streams application configuration
* Consistent region support to achieve at-least-once semantic where appropriate
* SSL connection
* Nullable column with optional type support

+ What's new

This is an overview of changes for major and minor version upgrades. For details, see the releases in public [https://github.com/IBMStreams/streamsx.eventstore/releases|GitHub].

++ What is changed in version 2.4.2

* Third-party library updated to resolve security vulnerability CVE-2020-11612 (netty-all: 4.1.52.Final)

++ What is changed in version 2.4.1

* Improved error handling in EventStoreSink.updateInsertSpeedMetrics

++ What is changed in version 2.4.0

* Client library updated for Db2 EventStore 2.0.0.5

++ What is changed in version 2.3.4

* Client library updated for Db2 EventStore to resolve memory leak issue

++ What is changed in version 2.3.2 and 2.3.3

* Globalization support: Messages updated

++ What is changed in version 2.3.1

* Globalization support: Introduced fallback message for non-translated error message

++ What is changed in version 2.3.0

* Client library updated for Db2 EventStore 2.0.0.1
* Third-party library updated to resolve security vulnerability CVE-2019-12402 (netty-all: 4.1.42)

++ What is new in version 2.2.0

* Supports globalized messages with unique message IDs

]]></info:description>
        <info:version>2.4.2</info:version>
        <info:requiredProductVersion>4.3.0.0</info:requiredProductVersion>
    </info:identity>
    <info:dependencies/>
</info:toolkitInfoModel>
